Contact

glm8zs@virginia.edu

www.linkedin.com/in/lee-mayer-2a9b9781 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Patient Safety Nursing BLS

Lee Mayer

BSN, RN, CCRN-CSC

Baltimore, Maryland

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Nursing, Critical Care, Basic Life Support (BLS), Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS), and Patient Safety. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science (BS) focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from University of Virginia.

Experience

University of Maryland Baltimore Student Registered Nurse Anesthetist (SRNA) June 2018 - Present (2 years 1 month) Baltimore, Maryland Area

University of Maryland Medical Center Registered Nurse July 2014 - June 2018 (4 years) Cardiac Surgery Intensive Care Unit

Education

University of Maryland Baltimore

Doctor of Nursing Practice, Nurse Anesthesia · (2018 - 2021)

University of Virginia

Bachelor of Science (BS), Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2010 - 2014)